# Srikanth Lokini

## Software Developer

Address Hyderabad, Telangana, India

**Phone** 9959763018

**E-mail** srikanth.lokini@gmail.com

**WWW** Whatsapp Number: +91-9959763018 **LinkedIn** https://www.linkedin.com/in/srikanth-lokini-48b07886

Agile & result-oriented Technical Associate with 6+ years of proven experience in technical & data management solution to global clients including highly valued individuals and fast-growing organizations. Works at fast pace to meet tight deadlines. Enthusiastic team player ready to contribute to company's success.

#### **Skills**

- 1. Riversand Master Data Management/Product Information Management.
- 2. Microsoft Business Intelligence (SSIS & SSAS).
- 3. ASP.Net.
- 4. Microsoft Azure.
- 5. Software Deployment.
- 6. Issue troubleshooting.
- 7. Technical documents comprehension.

## **Profile & Responsibilities -**

#### Consultant - Infosys Limited India (November 2021 - Current)

- 1. Working as Team Lead for the client Ralph Lauren (Riversand 8.x application). Maintaining the home/digital/ip-merge retail items for RL.
- 2. Managing team of 8, daily sync up call with customer and team.
- 3. Getting the requirement from customer, then accordingly helping Development teams to develop the application, and helping them to debug the issue while working on the code. Using the JIRA tool, MDM tool.
- 4. Resolve Client facing issues on daily basis with another support team.

# **Application Support engineer – Riversand (Syndigo) Technologies India PVT Ltd (**Jun 2021 – Nov 2021)

- 1. Responsible for managing support tickets from various clients on Riversand 8.x application
- 2. Responsible for debugging, maintaining, and reporting bugs to implementation teams.
- 3. Participating in platform and code rollouts/upgrade plans along with following mandated technical change procedures to maintain smooth transitions to clients.

Application Development Senior Analyst - Accenture Solutions PVT Ltd Hyderabad India (April 2016 - Jun 2021)

- 1. Responsible for developing and supporting Riversand 8.x application
- 2. Responsible for gathering client requirements and developing the Riversand application from scratch.
- 3. Responsible for working with inbound integration team (TIBCO) to get data from SAP.
- 4. Responsible for working with outbound integration team (TIBCO) to send data to salesforce application and e-commerce websites.

#### **Work History**

#### 2021-11-Current

#### Project - Master Data Management – Ralph Lauren

Technical Lead/Support Lead (Consultant) - Infosys Limited, India

- Having Daily Sync up with Customers to understand their requirements
- Managing team to clarify doubts and helping in delivering the requirements smoothly.
- Having Production Daily Sync up calls to resolving the Incidents (Service Now) created by Users and reporting them to Dev teams.

# 2021-06 **–** 2021-11

# Project - Master Data Management – (Multiple Clients like Zoo Plus, Sibelco, Auto Zone, Ralph Lauren, SC Johnson etc...)

Application Support Engineer - Riversand (Syndigo) Technologies pvt ltd., India

- Having Daily Support calls with a Team of 10 members.
- Working on JIRA tool to track and provide resolution for client created incidents and bugs.
- Need to work on RDW (test) tenants to fix the issues and report bugs if any to the engineering team to fix them in future upgrades.
- Ad hoc calls with Client support teams to identify the cause of the various issues and to provide limitation and SLA to them.

#### 2016-04 -2021-06

### Project - Master Data Management – SC Johnson

Application Development Senior Analyst - Accenture Solutions pvt ltd.

- Enhancing and supporting MSBI (SSIS & SSAS) applications for SC Johnson a manufacturer company for household products.
- Developing and supporting Riversand 8.x application for SC Johnson Product data.
- Daily calls with Client to gather functional requirements and to prepare a Functional design Document.
- Daily Support calls to identify and fix the issues both with vendor and customer.

## **Education**

2011 - 2015 B.E: Electrical & Electronics Engineering

Vasavi College of Engineering (Osmania university) – Hyderabad.

Percentage: 77.56

2009 - 2011 Intermediate

SVS Junior college- Hanamkonda.

Percentage: 92.2

2004 - 2009 High School

Carmel Convent high school I- Elkathurthy.

**Certifications** 

2020-10 Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900)-Microsoft Certified